[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Live Forever]
[Episode 16]
As long as he dies,
you two will love each other forever.
Then my sister's sacrifice won't be in vain.
Xiao He!
Sister!
♪ I was here ♪
Sister.
Qiu.
♪ Now I have to go ♪
Xiao He.
Sister!
You're alive!
You've grown up.
What did I tell you?
What are we?
We are Tree Spirits.
♪ I won't fall in a cage ♪
We can't hurt people.
♪ Missing old days ♪
Then what are you doing right now?
♪ I'll be there ♪
I...
But...
♪ I will hold my ground here ♪
But he took you away first!
He separated us!
♪ Let others say what they please ♪
General Yu from the past is already dead.
♪ The road ahead holds a bright scenery ♪
Now he is Lin Huai.
♪ I stop right here ♪
If you kill him,
you'll only add to your own sins.
But...
But he destroyed everything we had!
♪ Now I have to go ♪
He destroyed the lover you blessed!
He destroyed our home!
♪ I will live on ♪
I just want you to be safe.
♪ Let others say what they please ♪
You got your memory back?
To be precise,
it's the me from my past life.
We osmanthus Tree Spirits
only form our spirit cores
after waking from chaos to understand the world.
If the core leaves the body,
we must return to our roots
and wait to sprout again.
That's nice.
Life and death are in your own hands.
But...
the power of immortality in you and Song Yiqiu
is fading.
Is it because the painting Autumn Moon in the Forest bloomed?
From the moment it bloomed,
time for you and Song Yiqiu was released.
The more flowers bloom,
the closer you get to the end.
I regret it.
You regret it?
Regret falling in love with Song Yiqiu?
Regret loving her and
ending the immortality...
Do you know?
When she lay in my arms,
her wound not healing,
bleeding endlessly,
I finally realized
how cruel ending immortality is.
For the past 3,000 years,
we only parted in life.
But in the years to come,
we will eventually be parted by death.
So 3,000 years of time
didn't make you happy.
If only...
If only you could live like ordinary people,
experiencing birth, aging, sickness, and death...
maybe you could love and stay together like before,
and grow old together.
Maybe if I stop now,
there's still time.
Sister,
you will definitely love it here.
There are flowers everywhere.
They call it landscaping.
Sister,
I saw them today.
That pair of lovers.
The ones
you blessed with your spirit core.
Sister,
I learned a new way to weave flower crowns today.
Sister!
Xiao He.
I thought you were going to leave me again.
Why are you crying again?
I'm right here, aren't I?
I saw this.
When I tried to teach you as a kid,
you wouldn't learn.
Now you figured it out yourself.
Still as cute as ever.
Not as cute as you.
All of his vitals are returning to normal.
Medically speaking,
he's out of danger.
But he still hasn't woken up.
It's been so long.
Why isn't he awake yet?
That's the problem.
His cerebral cortex activity
is higher than a normal state.
To be precise,
his consciousness
is fighting against waking up.
I see.
Got it.
Thank you, doctor.
Talk to him more.
Call me if you need anything.
Thanks.
Mr. Ning.
Manager Qing Yuan,
why are you here?
I heard Miss Song was ill,
so I came by on behalf of the auction house.
Just a little something.
Thank you.
Miss Song is
recovering very quickly.
She's already out of bed and walking.
The one
lying there is...
Director Lin was also injured?
They were robbed on the road.
They were just startled.
They didn't suffer any major injuries.
Good to hear they're okay.
So,
Miss Song and Director Lin are quite close.
The way she looks at him is very different.
Looks like
you have some strong competition.
In an auction, the highest bidder wins.
But in love,
sometimes it's not about who bids the highest,
but about
who is more sincere.
Good luck to you.
Lin Huai.
Lin Huai,
do you know that
when I saw you again,
looking so free and vibrant,
I was so happy?
Because
this is the life your past self
fought so hard for.
It's so great!
You're warm,
and alive.
It's so great.
But I didn't expect
that you, like us,
have been trapped for 3,000 years.
None of us are
truly living,
nor have we ever truly lived.
Forget all this, Lin Huai.
When you wake up this time,
just be the Lin Huai you are now.
I hope in this lifetime,
you can live your life well.
Enjoy your life.
Qiu.
Qing Yuan from the auction house
came to see you.
Here are the flowers and fruits she brought.
Word travels fast with them.
Qiu,
you're not recovering as fast as before.
Please take good care of yourself.
Ning Changyue,
let's talk.
No rush.
We can talk after you're discharged.
Ning Changyue!
I'll go buy you some food.
Where's my osmanthus cake?
I ate it.
Buy some more.
Go buy it!
Beg me.
Ning, we're back!
Where is he?
Upstairs maybe?
Ning!
Qiu,
his things are gone.
His phone won't connect either.
Your collection has been sold.
The proceeds have been deposited into your account.
Manager Qing Yuan,
do me a favor.
I
have to go on a long trip.
I have some pieces
I'd like the auction house to sell for me.
Sure, Mr. Ning.
When the time comes,
the funds will be deposited
into the account you left with us.
Deposit it into Song Yiqiu's account.
Okay.
Pulling this trick again, Ning Changyue.
Qiu.
You're quite generous.
Qiu,
everything's done.
I'm exhausted.
Moving all this stuff here...
I'm telling you,
was no joke.
But
why did we move them to the riverbank?
In this weather, they'll get damp easily.
These are antique trunks.
They shouldn't touch the ground for too long.
By the way,
does Ning know?
Should we let him know?
Open them.
Open them? Okay.
This...
Qiu,
all these things look so valuable!
Throw them away.
Throw them away?
Wait,
Qiu,
could this be some...
Southern Qin bronze ware?
No, we can't throw this away.
Wait,
Qiu.
Why are you throwing away all these treasures?
Don't!
This is worth a lot of money!
Seriously,
why are you throwing away
such precious things?
Both of you think these are treasures.
Then you take them!
But...
Okay, let's dump them...
dump them.
All of them.
Don't worry.
I... I'll help you throw them?
Tang Dynasty pearls?
Throw away?
This...
This is top-tier yellow jade from the Song Dynasty.
Throw this too.
This whistle...
Can't really tell what this is.
This is Song... Song Dynasty?
Tang Dynasty? Song Dynasty?
Stupid brain, think fast!
Think fast!
What dynasty is this?
♪ Hard to write destiny in a few scrolls ♪
♪ Karma remains incomplete ♪
♪ Past memories burn to ashes at sunset ♪
♪ Cooling the old window sill ♪
♪ Gazing across lifetimes the obsession won't break ♪
♪ Who can bear the regret? ♪
Over the past 3,000 years,
♪ Three thousand years can't solve this game ♪
the mementos you casually tossed aside
or were forced to leave behind...
♪ Unwillingness in the cycle of reincarnation ♪
whatever I could recover
♪ Watching time flow ♪
is all right here.
♪ Hearing the years sigh softly ♪
♪ Immortality still cannot bring fulfillment ♪
♪ Let fate tear everything apart ♪
Call me anytime.
♪ Our bond exists only because ♪
♪ I don't want to leave regrets behind ♪
So this is what you meant by...
♪ Willing to give up immortality ♪
our shared memories from the past 3,000 years.
♪ To face hardships together ♪
♪ Don't ask how absurd the ending may be ♪
♪ I only want to use this lifetime ♪
♪ To trade it for eternity ♪
♪ Could we find our happy ending? ♪
I thought you'd never blow it again.